

Jin Zao

## Contact

#### **Address**

20 Tak Fung Street, Hong Kong, Hong Kong

### WhatsApp

+86 18243300926

#### **Email**

jinzao.business@gmail.com

## Skills

- Development Languages(Python, PHP, JavaScript)
- Database and cache(MySQL, MongoDB, Oracle, SQLServer)
- Server (Apache, Nginx, IIS servers)
  - API (REST & SOAP)
  - Algorithms and data structures

# Full Stack Web Developer

My name is Jin Zao and I have experience for 6+ years in the back-end and front-end development.

My skills:

Development Languages(Python, PHP, JavaScript)

 ${\tt Database\ and\ cache(MySQL,\ MongoDB,\ Oracle,\ SQLServer)\ Server}$ 

(Apache, Nginx, IIS servers)
API (REST & SOAP) Development

Algorithms and data structures

Algorithms and data structures

My experience and responsibility are:

Development Specialist with 7 years of industry experience and knowledge of onboarding and training employees, effectively planning strategies to meet staff development requirements. Experienced in using learning management systems. Drives training and development across all levels of the company.

Self-motivated Web Developer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with the company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

Logical and results-driven Web Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps, and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with a calm and focused demeanor.

## Work Experience

04/2013 - 07/2018

## Talenox, Hong Kong, Hong Kong, China

Software Programmer

- Established network specifications and analyzed workflow, access, information and security requirements
- Implemented, developed and tested installation and update of file servers, print servers and application servers in all departments
- Standardized job tasks and trained junior team members on industry best practices and standards

07/2018 - Current

## Self-employed, Hong Kong

Full-Stack Developer

I have worked as a freelancer on the Internet. My experience in: Front-end development with React, Vue, Back-end development with Django, Laravel

### Education

04/2008 - 04/2012

The University of Hong Kong
Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Land	uages
	14440

English

— B2